{

"Users": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Which club is sometimes referred to as FC Hollywood?",
            "answer": "FC Bayern Munich",
            "wrong1": "Real Madrid",
            "wrong2": "Barcelona",
            "wrong3": "Manchester United"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "In football, which team has won the Champions League (formerly the European Cup) the most",
            "answer": "RealMadrid",
            "wrong1": "Barcelona",
            "wrong2": "Ac Milan",
            "wrong3": "Liverpool"

        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Which MLS franchise team does David Beckham own?",
            "answer": "Inter Miami",
            "wrong1": "LA Galaxy",
            "wrong2": "New England",
            "wrong3": "San Jose"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Who won the FIFA Women's World Cup in 2019?",
            "answer": "USA",
            "wrong1": "Germany",
            "wrong2": "France",
            "wrong3": "Spain"
        },

        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "After Juventus, AC Milan and Inter, with nine Scudettos, which team has won the most Serie A titles?",
            "answer": "Genoa",
            "wrong1": "Bologna",
            "wrong2": "Roma",
            "wrong3": "Torino"
        },

        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "I was the first Liverpool player to win the Ballon d'Or. I scored 40 goals for my country and have played in England and Spain.",
            "answer": "Michael Owen",
            "wrong1": "Robbie Fowler",
            "wrong2": "George Weah",
            "wrong3": "Igor Belanov"
        },

        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "With 365 goals, who holds the record for top Bundesliga goalscorer of all time?",
            "answer": "Gerd Muller",
            "wrong1": "Robert Lewandowski",
            "wrong2": "Mario Gomes",
            "wrong3": "Karl-Heinz Rummenigge"
        },

        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Which manager was famously said to have given players 'the Hairdryer Treatment'?",
            "answer": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
            "wrong1": "Jose Mourinho",
            "wrong2": "Arsene Wenger",
            "wrong3": "Pep Guardiola"
        },

        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Who was the player of the match in final of football world cup 1998?",
            "answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
            "wrong1": "Ronaldo",
            "wrong2": "Rivaldo",
            "wrong3": "Spain"
        },

        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "The fastest goal scored in Premier League history came in 7.69 seconds. Who scored it",
            "answer": "Shane Long",
            "wrong1": "Sadio Mane",
            "wrong2": "Robbie Fowler",
            "wrong3": "Danny Welbeck"
        },

        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "With 202 clean sheets, which goalkeeper has the best record in the Premier League",
            "answer": "Petr Cech",
            "wrong1": "Edwin Van Der Sar",
            "wrong2": "Peter Schmeichel",
            "wrong3": "David Seaman"
        },

        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "The record number of World Cup goals is 16, scored by who",
            "answer": "Miroslav Klose",
            "wrong1": "Ronaldo",
            "wrong2": "Pele",
            "wrong3": "Gerd Muller"
        },

        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "There have been two World Cup trophies. What was the name of the first",
            "answer": "Jules Rimet Trophy",
            "wrong1": "Lapis Lezuli Trophy",
            "wrong2": "Coupe Morek Trophy",
            "wrong3": "Alvaro Cunyo Trophy"
        },

        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Three people have won the World Cup as a player and as a coach. Mario Zagallo, Didier Deschamps and... can you name the third?",
            "answer": "Franz Beckenbaeur",
            "wrong1": "Didi",
            "wrong2": "Johan Cruijff",
            "wrong3": "Lothar Matthäus"
        },

        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Which Spanish club's nickname is Los Colchoneros, which translates to English as 'The Mattress Makers'",
            "answer": "Athletico Madrid",
            "wrong1": "Real Madrid",
            "wrong2": "Real Betis",
            "wrong3": "Athletic Bilbao"
        },

        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "Messi has spent his entire professional career at Barcelona, but what was his schoolboy team?",
            "answer": "Newell's Old Boys",
            "wrong1": "River Plate",
            "wrong2": "Boca Juniors",
            "wrong3": "Argentinos Juniors"
        },

        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "Ronaldo is synonymous with the No.7, but what other number did he wear at Real Madrid",
            "answer": "9",
            "wrong1": "8",
            "wrong2": "11",
            "wrong3": "6"
        },

        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "Messi wore the No.30 at the start of his Barca career and is now No.10. What other number has he worn for the club?",
            "answer": "19",
            "wrong1": "15",
            "wrong2": "11",
            "wrong3": "21"
        },

        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "Who is the only player to win the Champions League with three different clubs?",
            "answer": "Clarence Seedorf",
            "wrong1": "Marco Van Basten",
            "wrong2": "Frank Rijkaard",
            "wrong3": "Zinedine Zidane"
        },

        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "Which outfield player appeared in the Champions League final in three different decades?",
            "answer": "Ryan Giggs",
            "wrong1": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
            "wrong2": "Ronaldinho",
            "wrong3": "Fransesco Totti"
        },

        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "Which team was the first from the UK to win the European Cup?",
            "answer": "Celtic",
            "wrong1": "Nottingham Forest",
            "wrong2": "Liverpool",
            "wrong3": "Manchester United"
        },

        {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "Which player holds the record for most Champions League winners' medals?",
            "answer": "Francisco Gento",
            "wrong1": "Alfredo de Stefano",
            "wrong2": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "wrong3": "Sergio Ramos"
        },

        {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "With nine goals, who scored the most goals in a single European Championship tournament?",
            "answer": "Michel Platini",
            "wrong1": "Paulo Rossi",
            "wrong2": "Alan Shearer",
            "wrong3": "Johan Cruiff"
        },

        {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "The Euro 2000 final between France and Italy was decided by Golden Goal. Which player scored the goal?",
            "answer": "David Trezeguet",
            "wrong1": "Zinedine Zidane",
            "wrong2": "Patrick Viera",
            "wrong3": "Thierry Henry"
        },

        {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "Which Premier League winner’s father played rugby for Wales?",
            "answer": "Ryan Giggs",
            "wrong1": "Gareth Bale",
            "wrong2": "Daniel James",
            "wrong3": "Aaron Ramsey"
        },

        {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "Who scored the first ‘perfect hat-trick’ (left foot, right foot, and header) in the Premier League?",
            "answer": "Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink",
            "wrong1": "Robbie Fowler",
            "wrong2": "Eric Cantona",
            "wrong3": "Ryan Giggs"
        },

        {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "Which player went through the Ajax youth system, played for Ajax and became Assistant Manager at the club in 2011?",
            "answer": "Dennis Bergkamp",
            "wrong1": "Johan Cruiff",
            "wrong2": "Marco Van Basten",
            "wrong3": "Ruud Gullit"
        },

        {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "The winners of the UEFA Champions League and the UEFA Europe League compete for which sporting trophy?",
            "answer": "UEFA Super Cup",
            "wrong1": "UEFA Winners Cup",
            "wrong2": "UEFA Confederations Cup",
            "wrong3": "UEFA Champions Cup"
        },

        {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "Name the player that, aged forty, was the oldest World Cup winning captain?",
            "answer": "Dino Zoff",
            "wrong1": "Bobby Moore",
            "wrong2": "Carlos Alberto",
            "wrong3": "Cafu"
        },

        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "Who is the highest scorer in World Cup finals for the Netherlands, with seven goals?",
            "answer": "Johnny Rep",
            "wrong1": "Marco Van Basten",
            "wrong2": "Ruud Gullit",
            "wrong3": "Johan Cruiff"
        },

        {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "Which was the first FIFA World Cup Finals tournament to feature substitutes?",
            "answer": "Mexico 1970",
            "wrong1": "Brazil 1950",
            "wrong2": "France 1938",
            "wrong3": "Spain 1982"
        },

        {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "Which two teams competed in the first all-English major European Cup Final?",
            "answer": "Tottenham - Wolverhampton",
            "wrong1": "Nottingham - Leeds",
            "wrong2": "Liverpool - Nottingham",
            "wrong3": "Manchester United - Nottingham"
        }
    ]
}